Interact, Academic Computer Service Newsletter UP174
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Interact, Academic Computer Service Newsletter
1976 -- 1996
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Tufts Computing and Communications Services
UP174
1.0 Linear Feet
Arrangement
This collection is organized into one series.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains issues of Interact. It is the newsletter about campus computer services at Tufts. This newsletter went through several name changes, it began as the TCS newsletter, then became Centerfold, then Interact.
Biographical / Historical
The Tufts Computing and Communications Services was changed to be the University Information Technology (UIT) Division in 2005.
- Interact, Academic Computer Service Newsletter, 1976 -- 1996; 1979 -- 1996; UP174.001; 1.0 Linear Feet
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains issues of Interact. It is the newsletter about campus computer services at Tufts. This newsletter went through several name changes, it began as the TCS newsletter, then became Centerfold, then Interact.
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged chronologically
  Conditions Governing Access
  Open for research.
  - Interact, September, 1989; UP174.001.001.00001 (Box 1)
  - Interact, March, 1990; UP174.001.001.00002 (Box 1)
  - Interact, April, 1990; UP174.001.001.00003 (Box 1)
  - Interact, Winter, 1990 -- 1991; UP174.001.001.00004 (Box 1)
  - Interact, April, 1991; UP174.001.001.00005 (Box 1)
  - Interact, September, 1991; UP174.001.001.00006 (Box 1)
  - Interact, March, 1992; UP174.001.001.00007 (Box 1)
  - Interact, September, 1992; UP174.001.001.00008 (Box 1)
  - Interact, November, 1992; UP174.001.001.00009 (Box 1)
  - Interact, February, 1993; UP174.001.001.00010 (Box 1)
  - Interact, April, 1993; UP174.001.001.00011 (Box 1)
  - Interact, August, 1993; UP174.001.001.00012 (Box 1)
  - TCS Newsletter, October, 1993; UP174.001.001.00013 (Box 1)
  - Interact, Spring, 1995; UP174.001.001.00014 (Box 1)
    Volume 13, No 1 and 2.
  - Interact, August, 1995; UP174.001.001.00015 (Box 1)
  - Interact, October, 1995; UP174.001.001.00016 (Box 1)
  - Interact, December, 1995; UP174.001.001.00017 (Box 1)
  - TCS Newsletter, September, 1979; UP174.001.001.00018 (Box 1)
  - Interact, February, 1983; UP174.001.001.00019 (Box 1)
  - Interact, May, 1983; UP174.001.001.00020 (Box 1)
  - Centerfold, April, 1976; UP174.001.002.00001 (Box 2)
  - Centerfold, September, 1976; UP174.001.002.00002 (Box 2)
  - Centerfold, October, 1976; UP174.001.002.00003 (Box 2)
  - Centerfold, February, 1979; UP174.001.002.00004 (Box 2)
  - TSCS Newsletter, September, 1979; UP174.001.002.00005 (Box 2)
  - Interact, November, 1982; UP174.001.002.00006 (Box 2)
  - Interact, December, 1982; UP174.001.002.00007 (Box 2)
  - Interact February, 1983; UP174.001.002.00008 (Box 2)
  - Interact, March, 1983; UP174.001.002.00009 (Box 2)
  - Interact, May, 1983; UP174.001.002.00010 (Box 2)
  - Interact, September, 1983; UP174.001.002.00011 (Box 2)
  - Interact, October, 1983; UP174.001.002.00012 (Box 2)
  - Interact, November, 1983; UP174.001.002.00013 (Box 2)
  - Interact, December, 1983; UP174.001.002.00014 (Box 2)
  - Interact, January, 1984; UP174.001.002.00015 (Box 2)
  - Interact, March, 1984; UP174.001.002.00016 (Box 2)
  - Interact, May, 1984; UP174.001.002.00017 (Box 2)
  - Interact, January, 1985; UP174.001.002.00018 (Box 2)
  - Interact, September, 1985; UP174.001.002.00019 (Box 2)
  - Interact, January, 1986; UP174.001.002.00020 (Box 2)
  - Interact, March, 1986; UP174.001.002.00021 (Box 2)
  - Interact, April, 1986; UP174.001.002.00022 (Box 2)
  - Interact, May, 1986; UP174.001.002.00023 (Box 2)
  - Interact, September, 1986; UP174.001.002.00024 (Box 2)
  - Interact, October-November, 1986; UP174.001.002.00025 (Box 2)
  - Interact, July, 1996; UP174.001.002.00026 (Box 2)
  - Interact, November, 1983; UP174.001.003.00001 (Box 3)
  - Interact, December, 1983; UP174.001.003.00002 (Box 3)
  - Interact, September, 1985; UP174.001.003.00003 (Box 3)
  - Interact, January, 1986; UP174.001.003.00004 (Box 3)
  - Interact, March, 1986; UP174.001.003.00005 (Box 3)
  - Interact, April, 1986; UP174.001.003.00006 (Box 3)
  - Interact, May, 1986; UP174.001.003.00007 (Box 3)
  - Interact, June-July, 1986; UP174.001.003.00008 (Box 3)
  - Interact, September, 1986; UP174.001.003.00009 (Box 3)
  - Interact, October-November, 1986; UP174.001.003.00010 (Box 3)
  - Interact, April, 1988; UP174.001.003.00011 (Box 3)
  - Interact, March, 1996; UP174.001.003.00012 (Box 3)
  - Interact, May, 1996; UP174.001.003.00013 (Box 3)
  - Interact, July, 1996; UP174.001.003.00014 (Box 3)